<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BetSportsOdds</string>

    <string name="about2">Bookmakers construct sports betting odds to show what the likely outcome of a game or event is.
    They also determine how much a gambler can profit from betting on an event at that sportsbook.
    They are frequently impacted by Vegas odds, particularly in sports.</string>

    <string name="about1">The action of forecasting sports results and putting a wager on the outcome is known as sports betting.
        The most popular sports to gamble on vary by culture, with association football, American football, basketball, baseball, hockey, track cycling,
        auto racing, mixed martial arts, and boxing receiving the vast majority of wagers at both the amateur and professional levels.
        Non-athletic events such as reality show competitions and political elections, as well as non-human contests such as horse racing, greyhound racing,
        and illegal, underground cockfighting, are all examples of sports betting. It is not commonplace for
        sports betting websites to accept bets on entertainment events such as the Grammys, Oscars, and Emmys.</string>

    <string name="chapter1">BASKETBALL</string>
    <string name="topic1">For bets to be active, all games must begin on the planned day (local time). An example is
If an inaccurate start time is announced on our website, a refund will be issued.
If the location of a game is changed, existing bets will stand as long as the home team remains.
labelled as such If the home and away teams for a listed match are switched, bets based on
the original listing will be null and void
Unless otherwise noted, all bets on a game include overtime.
If a game is suspended after the necessary amount of time has been played and not restarted, the game is forfeited.
a day, then regardless of whether the game is finished later, the score when the
The betting results will be determined if the game is interrupted.</string>
    <string name="topic2"></string>
    <string name="close_dialog" />


</resources>